

Profile

I successfully managed to combine two important things: work and passion showing myself that I can be self motivated. Energetic and resourceful dancer with several years of experience in art, performing in various locations in different parts of the world. I want professional re-conversion because I know I am capable of achieving great things, and I have a passion for IT and devices since I was a child. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

Employment History

Ballet/Folk Dancer, National Folk Ensemble "Transilvanya", Baia Mare

SEPTEMBER 2009 - PRESENT

- Performed preventative maintenance on office equipment and scheduled repairs as necessary.
- Served as a Choreographer for children and adolescence taking dance classes.
- Brought forth in-depth knowledge about several types of dance.

Volunteer/Coordinator, RoRec, Baia Mare

JULY 2010 - APRIL 2012

- Me and a team of 5 people, had to collect old/broken electric devices from people around the county.
- I was the man in the front, the one responsible for everything.
- · Achieved many skills in communication

Staging daily worker, ArtTradition, Baia Mare

JULY 2019 - NOVEMBER 2020

- A team of 4-6 other persons were putting together stages for all kind of shows around Romania.
- As a dancer, I assembled the stages for my own advantage.

Sales Assistant, LC.WAIKIKI Baia Mare

JULY 2017 - MAY 2018

- Greeted customers with a friendly and helpful attitude.
- Worked independently and collaboratively on projects.

Courses

Front-End Web Development, Informal School of I.T. Cluj Napoca

JANUARY 2021 - JUNE 2021

Web Development

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Reactis + Libraries
- NodeJS
- GitHub

Details

George Enescu Baia Mare, 430103 Romania +40 746 929 362

marius.ardeleann@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Romanian

DRIVING LICENSE

B since 2012

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

20.05.1994

Baia Sprie

Links

Facebook

GitHub

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Skills

Creativity

Computer Skills

Fast Learner

Multitasking

Communication Skills

Teamwork

Hobbies

Dancing, Traveling, Socializing, Gaming, Repairing laptops and other small to medium devices.

Languages

English

Romanian

Education

TBA, Informal School of IT, Cluj-Napoca

JANUARY 2021 - MAY 2021

- Aspiring Web Developer, ready to kick-off in this world of IT.
- I Like new and hard challenges
- I like seeing results imediately

7.50, Universitatea Tehnica din Cluj Napoca/Facultatea de Litere, Baia Mare

OCTOBER 2013 - JUNE 2016

- Here I studied about Ethnology and folklore.
- Perfected my English talking and writing skills

7.13, Colegiul Economic Nicolae Titulescu, Baia Mare

SEPTEMBER 2009 - MAY 2013

• Tourism and public alimentation profile